人生就像一条T台
Life is a runway
runway
T台
Listen here's what it's all about
听着事情是这样的
I tell you life is a runway
我告诉你人生就像T台
runway
T台
Time to bring what's on the inside out
是时候让内心的一切都显露出来
In to the light
走向光明
Life is a runway
人生就像T台
When you see it my way
当你从我的角度来看
Take all the good inside make it beautiful
把所有的美好都藏在心底
Fashion is a way to start showing what's in your heart
时尚是一种开始 展示你的内心
Call it superficial I call it irrefutable
就算是肤浅吧 我称之为无可辩驳
Oh  oh   oh wha oh
Oh oh oh wha oh Oh oh wha oh
Life is a runway
人生就像T台
You can be the girl
你可以做那个女孩
That you want to be
你想成为的那个人
With a little love And some accessories
心怀一点爱 还有一些配饰
Don't be scared to show you have personal style
不要害怕展示你的实力和个人风格
Just go do your thing You'll make everyone smile
去做你的事吧 你会让每个人微笑
You can be the girl
你可以做那个女孩
That you want to be
你想成为的那个人
With a little love And some accessories
心怀一点爱 还有一些配饰
Don't be scared to show you have personal style
不要害怕展示你的实力和个人风格
Just go do your thing You'll make everyone smile
去做你的事吧 你会让每个人微笑
Life is a runway
人生就像一条T台
runway
T台
I'll show you what it's all about
我会让你明白这一切的真谛
I tell you life is a runway
我告诉你人生就像T台
runway
T台
Time to bring what's on the inside out
是时候让内心的一切都显露出来
In to the light
走向光明